Previously on "Criminal Minds"...
"犯罪心理"前情提要
We're taking you home.
我來接你回家
Garcia: Do you really think that he can handle it,
你覺得他能扛得住嗎
I mean, all that Reid's been through?
Reid經歷了那麼多磨難?
We all know what that can do to the psyche of an inmate.
我們都知道囚犯的精神狀態會被影響
Scratch has surfaced again,
抓撓先生再次現身
this time at Jack's school,
這次出現在Jack的學校
which is why Hotch and Jack have now entered the program.
所以Hotch和Jack被保護了起來
Witness protection.
證人保護計劃
We might have a new lead on Mr. Scratch.
我們有抓撓先生的新線索
***
Reid已出獄且想見你 他把母親安置 在FBI安全屋過夜 回短信獲取地址
This text, it's a trap. Let's go.
這條短信是個陷阱 我們走吧
Guys?
大伙?
Don't go to voice mail.
別進留言信箱 別進留言信箱
This is SSA Emily Prentiss. I can't take your call right now, so...
我是Emily Prentiss高級探員 現在暫時無法接聽電話 所以...
Hey, I came as soon as I could.
嘿 我已最快速度趕來
- What's wrong? - They're gone.
- 怎麼了? - 他們都沒了
They're all gone.
全部失聯
- I'll drive. - Yeah.
- 我開車 - 好
Correct. Penelope Grace Garcia,
對 Penelope Grace Garcia
technical analyst, badge number 0019er0.
技術分析員 工號0019er0
I am with international response team
我與國際應急組的
special agent Matt Simmons.
特別探員Matt Simmons一起
Yeah. I know, but SSA Spencer Reid
嗯 我知道 但Spencer Reid探員
hasn't been reinstated yet, so...
還未被復職 所以...
Oh, my god, I know this is protocol,
老天 我知道這是程序
but you need to stop asking me questions
但你能別再問東問西
and send backup to the coordinates I just gave you right now, please...
馬上派增援到我給你的坐標 求求你
And medical.
還要叫救護車
Send lots of medical.
大量救護人員
No, no...
不要...
Ok. Come on. I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you.
好 我扶你 我扶你
Jag-off ambushed us,
那混蛋埋伏了我們
didn't even see him coming.
完全沒有料到
All right. We got to get you off that leg, ok?
我們扶你躺下 好吧?
No, no. I'm fine. I'm fine.
不用 我還好
I'll flag down the cavalry.
我去指揮救援車輛停車
You go check on the team.
你們去查看其他隊員
Yes, the team,
對 其他隊員
the team, the team.
我們團隊 隊員
- What can I do? - I can't see.
- 我能幫到什麼? - 我看不見了
What can I do? How can I help?
要我做什麼? 怎麼幫你?
I can't see. Ugh!
我看不見了 嗷!
Wait. All right. I see it, ok? I see it.
等等 好 我看見了
You got some broken glass in your scalp, JJ, ok?
你頭皮上有些碎玻璃 JJ
Just hold this till the ambulance comes, all right?
在救護車來到前抵著這個 好嗎?
- It'll be here soon. - Stephen?
- 救護車很快到 - Stephen?
Stephen?
Stephen?
He's gone. He's gone.
他走了 他走了
I can't leave him alone like this.
我不能把他扔在這裡
Luke! Luke!
Luke! Luke!
Tara, can you tell me where you're hurt?
Tara 能告訴我你哪裡受傷了嗎?
Um, I think I'm going into shock.
我好像快要休克
Ok. All right. I got you.
好 我來照顧你
Tara, we're gonna warm you up, all right?
Tara 我們幫你暖和起來 行嗎?
Bleeding internally, but we'll get some blood to your brain.
內出血 但我們會保證你的腦部供血
All right. Listen.
好 聽著
You're gonna want to go to sleep.
你會很想睡覺
We can't let you do that. You got to stay with us, ok?
但我們不准你睡 你得醒著 好嗎?
Stay with us. Over here!
好好醒著 這邊!
Those spike strips took out our two SUVs.
這些釘刺把我們兩輛SUV逼停
Then the truck blindsided us.
然後卡車側撞了我們
We have 6 agents that are...
我們一共六名探員...
Where's Emily?
Emily在哪裡?
Where am I?
我在哪裡?
You were in a car crash, a bad one.
你遭遇了車禍 情況嚴重
Oh, my god, what happened?
老天 發生什麼事了?
Your SUV sustained the brunt of the impact.
你們的SUV遭受劇烈撞擊
Specifically, you sustained it.
特別是你 受傷嚴重
Do you remember?
你還記得嗎?
No. I...
不記得 我...
Wait. Yeah. My team.
等等 對 我的小隊
Take... take it easy, Agent Prentiss.
別緊張 Prentiss探員
Got you stabilized, but you got to stay put.
給你上了鎮靜劑 你得好好躺著
Where am I? This isn't a hospital.
我在哪裡? 這不是醫院
I've been in enough hospitals.
我已經入院很多次
I know how they sound, how they smell,
熟知醫院的聲音和氣味
so where the hell am I?
我到底在哪裡?
You're being taken care of.
你會受到悉心照顧
We both are.
我們都是
Wait. What... what does that mean?
等等 什麼意思?
I don't understand you.
我不明白
Yeah. She's conscious.
嗯 她醒了
Well, hello, Emily.
你好 Emily
Son of a bitch.
王八蛋
It's nice to meet you, too, finally.
我也很高興見到你 終於
Did you grab all of us, huh?
你把我們都抓了嗎?
Are we all here? Luke! JJ!
我們都在這裡? Luke! JJ!
No. It's just you.
沒有 只有你而已
Your team is fine, by the way.
順便一提 你的隊員都沒事
Excuse me. I take that back.
抱歉 我收回前面這句話
The truck I drove into your team
我開的卡車撞你們團隊
did kill SSA Stephen Walker...
把Stephen Walker探員撞死了
Whiplash, tragic, leaves behind a wife
頸部屈伸過度 悲劇了 據我所知
and two children, I believe.
留下了妻子和兩名孩子
- No. - That's good.
- 不要 - 很好
Get it all out.
想哭就哭出來
I will make sure you fry for this.
我保證會讓你坐上電椅
Will you?
真的咩?
Well, maybe you should take a look
或許你應該先看看
at yourself first...
自己的境況
Because from where I'm standing,
因為在我看來
you won't be doing much of anything
你下半輩子
for the rest of your life.
基本什麼都幹不成
-=http://bbs. sfile2012=- Proudly Presents
<font color=#238E68-=伊甸園美劇=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流, 嚴禁用於商業途徑
Sync: YTET- °îµÂÖí
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯&校對: 米米粒愛小乖 時間軸: YTET-邦德豬
CRMININAL MINDS s13e01
犯罪心理 第十三季 第1集
"Hold on when there is nothing in you
"一無所有時請堅持下去
except the will which says, "hold on."
只要'堅持'的信念尚存"
Rudyard Kipling.
拉迪亞德．吉卜林(英國小說家)
- Spence. - You ok?
- Spence - 你還好嗎?
I'm...
我還好
I need to call Will.
我要打電話給Will
I did. I did. He's on the way.
我已經打了 他正在趕來
Right. Right.
好
Oh, Monica,
噢 Monica
Stephen's wife.
Stephen的妻子
Someone needs to call her and tell them.
得有人打給她 告知噩耗
Rossi's refusing treatment until he speaks to both of us.
Rossi拒絕治療 直到跟我們說完話
What's going on?
怎麼了?
Shut up and listen. All right.
- 閉嘴 聽我說 - 好
First, you, go through my pants pockets and find my keys.
首先 你去翻我的褲袋找到鑰匙
Second, you, you're back on the team.
然後 你 即刻復職歸隊
Not sure I should be.
不確定我應不應該
Has the director approved that?
局長批准了嗎?
I'm making the calls now.
現在聽我的
I'll take the heat. You're back on the team.
責任我來負 你馬上歸隊
I got them.
找到
There's a little one there
上面有一條小鑰匙
to a file cabinet in my office.
能打開我辦公室的文件櫃
You following me?
明白嗎?
Yeah. Following you.
嗯 明白
Inside, there's Chicago Bears season tickets.
裡面有芝加哥小熊隊的季票
When you get them, you call Matt Simmons.
你拿到後 打電話給Matt Simmons
I promised him those tickets.
我答應了給他這些票
They must have given him something
他們在救護車上一定給他打了葯
in the ambulance to make him loopy.
整個人迷迷糊糊的
I'll get the doctor. We'll get him into surgery.
我去叫醫生 他得進行手術
Just shut up and listen.
閉嘴 聽我說
Now, Emily is missing. Stephen is dead.
現在Emily失蹤 Stephen已去世
As for you two ass clowns,
至於你們這倆蠢驢
you'll do me the courtesy of following my orders.
放尊重點 服從我的指揮
Your orders aren't making sense.
你的指揮完全不合理
Follow my orders, and then I'll go into surgery.
服從指揮 我才去做手術
This has got nothing to do with season tickets.
這跟季票沒關系
"Ass clown"?
"蠢驢"?
So Scratch hacked my phone tonight
今晚抓撓先生黑了我的手機
using something called a man in the middle attack.
使用了所謂的中間人攻擊
That means he's on a specific radio frequency.
代表他在用特定的無線頻率
And you're thinking he's using the same
你認為他用同一個無線頻率
radio frequency to activate these spikes.
來觸發釘刺機關
Well, he is a man of habit.
他是個按習慣行事的人
Maybe we can use that habit to locate him
或許我們能利用這習慣來找到他
and figure out...
搞明白...
This is how I profile.
我是這麼分析的
Oh, oh, oh. Hold. Freeze. Freeze.
噢 等等 停手
You just hit it. Hold on.
剛才找中了 等等
All right. Back it up.
好 往回一點
Booyah.
中了
Now we got the frequency.
現在我們找到了無線頻率
We just have to figure out
只需要搞清楚
where he's broadcasting it from.
他從哪裡發出訊號就行
Ok. That is easier said than done.
好 說來容易做起來難
Radio signals work on a preset range.
無線訊號的工作范圍是預先設定好的
We'll walk or drive in and out of proximity to it.
我們要在附近步行或駕車來回
And he could be bouncing it off multiple buildings.
而且還有可能通過樓宇進行反射
Yeah. That's also true.
嗯 很對
Ok. The least I could do is make sure Scratch
好 我能做的至少是保證抓撓先生
doesn't ambush us again, so the next time he goes live,
不能再次埋伏我們 下次他上線時
I'll set up some sort of signal, like...
我預設好某種信號 比如說...
***
警告
They have to take him to the hospital, anyway?
他們還是得送他去醫院?
Yeah. That's the proper procedure.
嗯 那是正常流程
Need a minute?
需要時間整理情緒嗎?
So, so badly, but...
非常非常需要 但是...
We have to help Emily.
我們得幫助Emily
Let's get to work.
開工吧
Taking a little mindfulness break?
想通過入定來休息?
Trying to control your breathing?
嘗試控制呼吸?
That's smart.
很聰明
It'll keep you sane...
能讓你保持理智...
And I need you sane.
我需要你保持理智
Oh, how rude. Excuse me.
手真笨 抱歉
Look. I'm only alive because you want something.
你有所求才留我一命
So what do you want?
你到底想要什麼?
Information that only you have.
只有你知道的情報
What are you waiting for, then?
那你還等什麼?
Dose me with your drugs, the ones that make me see
給我下葯 讓我看見
whatever delusion you suggest,
你想要的幻覺
and I'll tell you what you want.
然後我就會吐露一切
Hmm, I would love nothing more than that.
這是我再想不過的事了
Unfortunately, in your current physical condition,
但是很不幸 你目前的身體狀況
the sevoflurane and scopolamine
使用七氟醚和東莨菪鹼
would send you into a stroke.
會讓你中風
I guess we're at a stalemate, then.
看來我們陷入僵局了
No. I still have drugs that can make you talk,
沒有 我還有能讓你開口的葯
just different drugs.
其他種類的葯
This is morphine.
這是嗎啡
This is what is making your life
這是現在讓你過得
very livable right now.
舒服愉快的良葯
Without this...
如果不打嗎啡...
Your body will be on fire,
你的身體會灼熱難忍
and then you really will tell me
然後你會乖乖地供出
everything I want, no delusion necessary.
我想知道的一切 無需迷魂
I can't arrest him.
我無法逮捕他
- What? - Scratch.
- 什麼? - 抓撓先生
The second I see his face,
我一旦看見他的臉
I am going to kill him.
就會忍不住殺了他
I tried to tell Rossi not to put me back on the team.
我想說服Rossi不要安排復職
- You heard me. - Yeah. I did.
- 你也聽到的 - 嗯 聽到
What's wrong with me?
我到底怎麼了?
My guess is, it's been going on since prison,
我猜你進監獄就開始有這狀況
but you haven't had time to notice.
但你一直沒時間察覺
Every time you get stressed, you go into tunnel vision.
每一次壓力襲來 你的視野就變狹窄
That's why you're rubbing your palm into your eye.
所以你才用力搓眼睛
Yeah. What does that sound like, Reid?
嗯 聽起來像什麼 Reid?
- Sounds like PTSD. - PTSS.
- 像PTSD - PTSS
That's what they're calling it now,
現在改名字了
post-traumatic stress syndrome,
創傷後應激綜合征
because it's not a disorder.
因為這不是精神錯亂
It's an injury.
是受傷了而已
Well, what do I do? I mean, we're in crisis mode.
那我該怎麼辦? 我們都陷入危機了
I don't have time to process my emotional state.
沒有時間消化我的精神狀態
That's exactly when you make time, right?
所以才需要擠出時間面對 對吧?
You ask for help.
找人幫忙
There's no shame in that.
沒有什麼好羞恥的
- Rossi's office. - Yeah.
- Rossi的辦公室 - 嗯
- I'll handle that. - No.
- 我去處理 - 不是
There's someone in Rossi's office.
有人在Rossi的辦公室裡
Ok. Now that we are secure,
好 現在我們的對話安全了
I got that for Rossi last year.
我去年送給Rossi的
Not only is it a cigar case,
不僅僅是個雪茄盒
but it's also a Faraday case.
還是個法拉第籠
It blocks all radio and cell signals.
屏蔽所有無線電和手機訊號
I think Scratch might be listening in on us
我覺得抓撓先生可能通過手機
with our cell phones, even when they're off.
在監聽我們 即使關機也阻止不了
That explains why Rossi was so cagey in the hospital.
這解釋了Rossi在醫院時 為何吞吞吐吐的
All right. Let's find these tickets.
好 我們找季票吧
What is this?
這是什麼?
Stephen was brought on board for one reason.
Stephen的加入只為一個目的
That was to catch Scratch.
那就是逮捕抓撓先生
That is his entire investigation into him.
這是他對抓撓先生的全部研究資料
He kept all his records off site,
所有檔案他都不放在辦公室
updating Prentiss and Rossi through hard copies.
有新進展就給Prentiss 和Rossi復印件
If it's off the cloud, Scratch can't hack it.
若沒有存進雲盤 抓撓先生就黑不了
- Have you guys read it? - No.
- 你們看過了嗎? - 沒有
Prentiss ordered it compartmentalized,
Prentiss指示了分隔存放
eyes-only clearance, but she also felt
申請許可才能閱讀 但她認為
there should be at least one failsafe who wasn't part of the BAU
至少需要一名非BAU人員 做故障保險
who knew about it just in case of emergency.
了解此案 以防萬一
That's why Garcia called me.
所以Garcia才打電話給我
All right. Let's dig in.
好 我們開始調查吧
I mean, this may be our only chance at stopping this bastard.
這可能是我們阻止那雜種的唯一途徑
Look. Ok. Look. Ok.
聽著 好啦 我招
Whatever it is, we can discuss it.
無論你想知道什麼 都好商量
You don't have to do this.
不用折磨我啦
Just give me the morphine, ok,
給我打嗎啡 好嗎
and... and... just...
還有
You can ask whatever you want.
你想問什麼都行
It was our investigation into you? Is that it?
想知道我們對你的調查 是吧?
Is that what you want to know?
你想知道的是這個嗎?
Tangentially.
不太相關
Oh! Nngh! Then what?
噢! 唔! 那是什麼?
Tell me. Tell me. Then I'll tell you.
告訴我 我都跟你說
It's that simple.
就是那麼簡單
Tell me, and I'll tell you.
告訴我 然後我跟你說
Yeah. I believe you will now.
嗯 我相信你會說實話了
There is a certain dearly departed team member of yours
你們中某個已離開的成員
that I would like to discuss with you.
是我希望與你談談的話題
- Stephen. - No, not Stephen.
- Stephen - 不對 不是Stephen
This one isn't dead, at least not yet.
他沒死 至少還沒死
This agent and I had a little tete-a-tete,
我和這名探員曾經面談過
and I crossed a line I shouldn't have.
當時我很不應該地越界了
I really couldn't help myself,
我真的忍不住
and I started to stalk his son,
然後我開始跟蹤他的兒子
and do you know what he did,
你知道他幹什麼了嗎
that coward?
那個縮頭烏龜?
He went into witness protection...
他進了證人保護計劃
And he has been very difficult to find ever since,
從此就再也找不著了
so that's what I want to know.
那才是我想知道的事
I want you to tell me where he is because I know you know.
我想你告訴我他在哪裡 因為我肯定你知道他的地址
No.
不要
Oh, stop. No.
閉嘴 不要
Yes, Emily.
沒錯 Emily
Where is Aaron Hotchner?
Aaron Hotchner在哪裡?
I don't know where Hotch is.
我不知道Hotch在哪裡
I don't.
我不知道
That's how WITSEC works.
證人保護計劃就是這樣
He has to be hidden from us
他的行蹤我們也不知道
because of men like you.
正因為有你這樣的人
Do you recognize this?
你認得這個嗎?
Well, it was a text exchange you had
這是你與幾台一次性手機
with a series of burner phones,
發短信的記錄
and a last text exchange between you
你和這名神秘男子
and this mystery man reads,
交換的最後一條短信這麼說
"Honduras connection is a go.
"洪都拉斯聯系可用
"Hunting down all leads to B-cap in DC.
"正在追蹤華府內B-cap的線索
Thanks. A.H."
謝謝 A.H."
Let's get down to the question at hand.
現在問題來了
Where is Hotch?
Hotch在哪裡?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等等等
He never gave me an address. All we did was text.
他沒告訴我地址 我們只是發短信而已
No. Last chance.
答錯 最後一次機會
Vermont.
佛蒙特
He's somewhere in Vermont.
他在佛蒙特州某處
Hi. I'm sorry.
嘿 對不起
You don't want to do that, Monica.
你不會希望這樣做 Monica
Ok. I'll come get you now.
好 我現在來接你
Stephen's wife?
Stephen的妻子?
Tell her I'm sorry.
告訴她我非常抱歉
Prentiss texted Hotch?
Prentiss給Hotch發過短信?
According to Stephen's documentation, yes.
根據Stephen的文件 沒錯
It must have been a coordinated attempt to share intel.
應該是約好了分享情報
Would Hotch have exposed himself like this?
Hotch會這麼冒險暴露身份嗎?
No, and neither would she. I mean, she wouldn't rely on a hackable app,
不會 她也不會這麼做 她不會用危險的手機應用
and she sure as hell wouldn't write, "A.H.," in a text.
而且一定不會在短信中寫下"A.H."
That defeats the purpose
這破壞了分區隔離調查的目的
It was a smoke screen.
這是個煙幕彈
Stephen had a background in counterintelligence.
Stephen有反情報背景
He must have designed this.
一定是他設計的
He faked the Hotch side of the conversation to entice Scratch to make a move.
他偽造了Hotch的短信 引誘抓撓先生出擊
The size and scale of which indicate desperation,
襲擊的規模與范圍暗示了絕望情緒
a desperation he hasn't shown after a year of hiding, so why now?
躲藏一年之久都無產生的絕望 為什麼現在突然絕望?
A.H. is a pretty big red flag.
A.H.是個好明顯的誘餌
Maybe that's what brought him out.
或許他為了這個而現身
Well, they used Hotch's initials in other texts before.
他們以前也在其他短信裡 用過Hotch名字的縮寫
Then they found something else,
後來他們發現了些別的事
something they knew would rattle him.
能夠激起抓撓先生不安的事
B-cap. What's B-cap?
B-cap 什麼是B-cap?
Geography maybe.
或許是某個地理概念
I mean, it's mentioned in relevance to DC.
因為跟華府一起被提到
Maybe its a code name for a partner.
或許是合作者的代號
- I can't see it. - Hey, no.
- 我想不通 - 嘿
Why don't we kick it over to the team?
我們去問問其他組員吧?
Maybe they can suss out...
或許他們能夠想出...
No. No time. Get out.
不 沒時間了 出去
What? Get out. Sorry.
- 啥? - 出去 抱歉
You, too. I'm really sorry, but get out.
你也是 很抱歉 但請出去
Let me get this, and then I'm gonna go.
讓我拿上手提 然後我就走人
It's ok. Ok.
好的 沒事
He's had a rough couple of months.
他過去幾個月深受折磨
Oh, my god, babe.
老天爺 寶貝
Oh, how are the kids?
孩子們怎樣了?
Oh, they're fine. They're fine.
他們很好 沒事
I didn't even wake them. I got your mom to come over.
我沒叫醒他們 請你媽媽過來照看著
- Oh, right. - Look at me.
- 好 - 看著我
How are you?
你怎麼樣?
Um, he... he gave me the front seat.
他讓我坐前排
Stephen did?
Stephen讓你坐?
Yeah. I was all set to sit in the back,
是啊 我本來是坐後排的
but he got there first, and I...
但他先上車了 我就
So is it time to call it?
是時候辭職了嗎?
That was the deal, right?
我們說好了 對吧?
If it got too scary, one of us could call it,
如果情況變得太可怕 其中一人可以叫停
not today, not this week after we find Emily.
但不是今時今日 不是在找到Emily之前
Well, if I remember,
如果我沒記錯
you would be a full-time mom,
你會成為全職母親
and I would run a breakfast place.
我就去開一家早餐店
Mm, and I'd go to all the PTA meetings.
嗯 我會參加各種各樣的家長會
You'd come home smelling like grease.
你帶著一股油煙味回家
It's tempting.
聽上去多吸引人啊
Hmm, yeah,
嗯 是啊
so do you want to call it?
你想讓我辭職嗎?
You see these rings?
你看到這對戒指了嗎?
We've worn them for 5 years,
我們戴了5年
but I've loved you for 10.
我愛上你超過10年
Hasn't been easy.
這一點都不容易
No, but I wouldn't trade a single day,
是啊 但我每天都不後悔
not even the awful ones like today...
就算像今日那麼糟糕也一樣
And I'll do whatever you want to do, but...
我會讓你隨心所欲 但
Oh, thank god.
噢 感謝上帝
Neither do I.
我也不想辭職
Get a room, you two.
注意影響啊 小倆口
Is my leg still attached?
我的腿還掛著吧?
Yeah.
對的
- Is Prentiss... - Nothing.
- 那Prentiss... - 渺無音訊
All right. I got to go. Luke's here.
好 我要走了 Luke來了
- Oh, Monica... - Don't.
- 噢 Monica... - 別
I can't.
我受不住
Where's my husband?
我丈夫在哪?
Oh, babe, what happened?
親愛的 發生什麼事了?
The kids are still asleep.
孩子們還在睡覺
How do I...
我該怎麼
I'll take care of it, ok?
我會處理好 知道嗎?
See you.
再見
Where is that place that you go to
你會去哪裡
to ground yourself?
釋放你自己?
I'd like to know.
我很想知道
So you can destroy it.
好讓你毀滅掉麼
See, I've read your case file.
我看過你的檔案
I've read about how your father was killed
我知道你父親是怎麼死的
when you were 13, and earlier,
那時你才13歲
you said something about crossing a line
我聽到你剛剛說自己越界了
when it came to stalking a child.
不得不跟蹤一名孩子
I realized Hotch's son Jack,
我想起Hotch的兒子Jack
he's 13 now, too.
他今年也是13歲
I'm not a pedophile.
我沒有戀童癖
I'm insulted by your inference.
你對我的推斷相當侮辱人
No. Your interest in Jack is clinical.
不 你對Jack感興趣是種試驗
You want to see what it will be like
你想看看結果將會怎樣
if he grows up without his father like you did.
如果他如你般在成長中失去父親
That's what I've been focusing on.
這正是我關注的重點
After you kill Hotch,
在你殺掉Hotch後
you'll never leave Jack alone. Am I right?
你可不會放過Jack 我說得對嗎?
You are.
說對了
Then let me tell you something, Peter.
那我實話告訴你吧 Peter
I've died before protecting a child.
我曾經為了救孩子差點沒命
That was a child I barely knew,
那孩子我根本不認識
but Jack, I love Jack.
但提到Jack 我喜歡Jack
I've watched Jack grow up.
我看著Jack長大
I will not betray him or his father,
我不會出賣他或者他父親
so it doesn't matter what you do to me.
無論你對我上什麼刑
I will not break.
我都不會屈服
Let me test that resolve.
讓我考驗一下你的信念吧
You make an interesting point.
你的決心令人感動
I need a plan "B."
我得想想別的辦法
Hey, you, come here...
嘿 你 快過來
Just for a second.
一會就好
Please, I just need a second.
求你了 一會就好
This I might be able to help with.
這一條我可能知道
Prentiss' last text had to do with Honduras.
Prentiss最後一條短信 提到洪都拉斯
Scratch's last known sighting before tonight was Honduras.
今夜前抓撓先生的最後目擊地 正是洪都拉斯
Right, and we thought Scratch fled there
對啊 在墨西哥將謀殺案 栽贓給Reid之後
after he framed Reid for murder in Mexico.
我們認為抓撓先生逃到那邊
Right. Prentiss asked the IRT to contact
Prentiss有讓IRT聯系
our central American sources just to see if we could find anything.
中美洲的線人 想看看有沒有線索
Now, we never did.
然而我們沒找到
We also never stopped to ask why Scratch
我們一直在想抓撓先生
was in Honduras in the first place.
為何會在洪都拉斯出現
Reid'll figure this out.
Reid會想明白
He's really amazing at this kind of thing.
他非常擅長解決各類謎團
B-cap is short for Banisters caapi.
B-cap是南美卡皮木的簡稱
It's a plant, specifically a hallucinogen that's found
那是一種植物 泡成茶又稱死藤水
in a tea called ayahuasca.
帶有致幻劑成分
We worked a couple of those cases, I think.
我們處理過不少類似案件
If I remember, it's like peyote.
沒記錯的話 應該跟鳥羽玉差不多
Yeah, in multiple ways.
是的 共同之處很多
They're similar legally in that taking them
服用也不算違法
is considered a religious practice,
因為它們經常用於宗教儀式
and pharmacological, they're similar in that
葯理學上它們成分相似
both drugs cause you to hallucinate
兩種葯物都會致幻
intense, geometric patterns and vomit a lot.
視覺出現斑點 大量嘔吐
Ok. What does this have to do with Scratch?
這跟抓撓先生有何聯系?
Well, Scratch has a cocktail of disassociative drugs
抓撓先生擅長混合各類致幻葯物
to induce delusions, but a mathematical mind
進行洗腦 但像他那麼精明
like his would always be looking for ways to tweak and improve the formula.
一定會不斷調整改進配方
So he went to Honduras to look for it.
所以他跑到洪都拉斯找木頭
He then brought it back to DC to experiment with it.
然後帶回華盛頓做實驗
Stephen and Emily came to the same conclusion
Stephen和Emily也作出同樣推測
and tried to pretend like they were hot on his trail.
並假裝已經差不多要抓到他了
We need to track down all practitioners of the ceremony in the district...
我們要追蹤區域內所有儀式執行人
Shamans, gurus, overnight religions
薩滿 精神導師 剛建立
that just hung their first shingle.
正要大張旗鼓的新教派
He could be using one of their volunteers
他有可能利用某位志願者
as a partner, either witting or unwitting.
作為他的搭檔 無論對方是否知悉
What?
怎麼了?
You threw a book at a window. It was jarring.
你把書砸到玻璃上 嚇壞人了
Took me 60 minutes to deduce
我花了60分鍾才想出
what should have taken me 60 seconds,
60秒就該明白的問題
and if Emily dies because I was too slow,
如果Emily因為我的遲鈍而死
I'll be throwing a lot more than books.
我砸的可不止是書了
Please. Please help me.
求你了 幫幫我
You don't even have to get me out of here.
你不用把我放出去
Just make a phone call. You can use my phone.
打個電話就好 用我的手機
Call 911, leave the phone, and run.
撥911 放著 然後離開
I can't do that.
恕難從命
I won't tell them you were involved.
我不會把你的事告訴警察
It's not that simple.
沒那麼簡單
You said we were both being taken care of.
你說我們都會被悉心照顧
You mean trapped.
是指關在這裡吧
He has your family, doesn't he?
他抓了你的家人 對吧?
Ok. My team can rescue them.
我的團隊可以救他們出來
It's what we do.
我們的工作就是救人
- I have to go. - No. Please.
- 我要走了 - 別 求你了
- I can't. - Take my phone.
- 我做不到 - 拿走我的手機
Please take my phone.
請拿走我的手機
It's so hard to find good help these days.
這年頭要找好心人幫助很難哦
It seems like, no matter what,
似乎無論如何
I'm left to do all the dirty work.
我都得親自去幹臟活累活
What is that?
那是什麼?
Is that the morphine?
是嗎啡嗎?
It's amphetamine.
是安非他命
I figured out my plan "B."
我想出了新辦法
I can't torture the answers out of you,
既然折磨你得不到答案
so I'll simply stop your heart instead.
那只好直接以死相逼
If you want to live,
如果你還想活命
tell me what I want to know.
把我要知道的告訴我
Where's Hotch, Emily?
Hotch在哪 Emily?
Where's Hotch?
Hotch在哪裡?
Come on.
快醒醒
*
生於1970年11月12日 死於2011年3月7日 死於2011年9月21日
Of course.
果然
I get it now.
我懂了
That's it.
太好了
Please,
求你了
tell him what he wants.
說出他要的信息吧
If you tell him what he wants,
如果你把他想知道的供出來
this can all be over.
就不用繼續受罪
He'll release my family, and...
他就會釋放我家人 然後
And then I can help you, ok?
然後我也會幫你 好嗎?
What? What's that?
什麼? 你想說什麼?
Go get him.
叫他來
Ok, so apparently, the only local place
看來本地唯一使用卡皮木的
using b-cap is the church of the herbal sacrament,
是草葯聖禮教堂
"where you can find everything
"你想探知的一切精神需求"
"for your spiritual needs that only ayahuasca can fulfill."
"死藤水都能滿足"
Walk me through what's gonna happen when we get there.
告訴我去那邊會遇到什麼妖魔鬼怪
We ask questions, and we come home.
我們會問問題 我們會平安回家
No creepy weirdness?
沒有毛骨悚然?
No weirdness.
沒有毛骨悚然
Good because I'm about full up
太好了 我今晚經歷的驚悚
in the creepy weirdness department for one night.
已經夠多
I've seen the face of God.
我看到了上帝的臉容
I've seen it.
我看到了
So much for no creepy weirdness.
這還不叫毛骨悚然麼
Scratch's radio signal.
抓撓先生的無線電信號
Clear. Come on in.
安全了 進來吧
Mother lode.
大金礦啊
Yeah. Looks like we found Scratch's I.T. department, no Scratch.
我們找到了抓撓先生的資訊中心 但沒找到他
Yeah, but this is where he's been doing everything...
但這正是他操縱一切的地方
Hacking me, hacking our phones,
黑我的電腦 黑我們的手機
the whole tamale...
打包送上種種陷阱
And, just like you predicted,
然後如你所料
he's been bouncing the signal
他在多棟大樓之間
off multiple buildings.
隨機跳頻發射信號
We're close, Matt.
差不多接近他了 Matt
They sent me to talk some sense into you.
他們讓我來勸你
Can't help by lying down,
躺著可幫不上忙
and I hear Tara's waking up.
我聽說Tara已經醒了
Do you... do you want me to find you some crutches or something?
你需要我給你找根拐杖之類的嗎?
I don't need them. I got you.
我不用拐杖 有你就行
Scratch. Scratch took Emily.
抓撓先生擄走了Emily
I saw him. Yeah. We know.
- 我看見他了 - 我們知道
We're looking for him.
我們正在找他
He dosed her.
他給她下葯了
In the SUV while she was knocked out?
她在車裡暈過去時被下葯?
Yeah.
是的
He brought his gas with him.
他把自己的迷幻氣體帶來了
Your legs are broken.
你兩條腿都斷了
Your right arm is broken.
你右臂骨折
You're in severe traction, and you're paralyzed.
你在接受深度牽引 你已經癱瘓了
You feel unimaginable agony
你感受到全身無比痛苦
all over your body unless I give you high doses of painkiller.
除非我給你止痛葯
She would wake in a delusion he'd have total control over.
她醒來時會處於他控制的幻覺中
He think she knows where Hotch is, so he's trying to trick her.
他認為她知道Hotch在哪 想要套出話來
She's one of the smartest people we know.
她是我們見過最聰明的人之一
She'd see through it.
她會識破
So Scratch would go even farther.
所以抓撓先生會變本加厲
Sometimes interrogators even simulate death.
有時審問者甚至會模擬死亡情景
Man, he could make it feel like the real thing.
他能讓人感受到自己真的死了
No. That wouldn't work.
不 沒效果的
Remember, Rossi, when Prentiss told us about when she died,
記得嗎 Rossi Prentiss告訴過我們
for real died, how for her,
她真正瀕死的體驗 對她而言
it was just dark and cold?
是又黑又冷的景象?
That's right.
是的
If he made her experience some
如果他刻意制造
out-of-body vision, she'd know it was a lie.
靈魂出竅的假象 她會看穿
Yeah. I get it.
果然 我懂了
Jareau, voice-over: He probably combined the delusion
他可能會把幻覺
with a classic prisoner interrogation tactic.
與典型審問策略相結合
At first, he would take away any chance of escape.
一開始 他不會給她任何逃跑機會
Then he would introduce somebody else and give her a sliver of hope.
然後引入另一個人 給予希望
It could be a second interrogator who is a nice guy.
那可能是第二名審問者 扮演好人
He's on his way, ok?
他馬上就來 聽到嗎?
That guy would be her blind spot.
那人會成為她的弱點
She'd trust him and then reveal something she shouldn't.
她會信任那個人 說出不該說的話
Ok? Ok?
聽到嗎? 聽到嗎?
Ok?
聽到嗎?
Yeah. Yeah. Ok.
好 好 聽到
Hey, what do you got, Matt?
嘿 有何發現 Matt?
Simmons, on phone: Well, we pinned down Scratch's
我們根據抓撓先生的
most likely location based on his radio frequency.
無線電頻率標注地圖
It's a warehouse in the district.
定位在區域內的一座倉庫
Garcia just texted the address.
Garcia剛把地址發過去了
She included Reid on the text.
她也發給Reid了
Reid's not in a good place.
Reid的狀態不太適合工作
I'm 10 out.
我10分鍾趕到
All right. So am I.
好的 我也過去
If I would've known that putting you
如果我早知道讓你到鬼門關轉一圈
at death's door would get you to talk,
你就會招供
I would've started with that.
我一開始就用這招
Now, are you ready to tell me where Hotch and Jack are?
現在你要告訴我 Hotch和Jack在哪了嗎?
Good. Go ahead.
來 說出來
They're at...
他們在
Tell me.
告訴我吧
8... 5...
8... 5...
FBI!
FBI!
Prentiss! Reid!
Prentiss! Reid!
Prentiss!
Prentiss!
Lower your weapon, damn it.
槍口放下 天啊
Where's Scratch?
抓撓先生在哪?
Oh, he's upstairs. Tag in here.
他在樓上 留在這裡吧
Simmons and Alvez can box him in.
Simmons和Alvez會把他抓住
No. I need to go find him.
不行 我要找到他
No, no, no, Spence. Please.
別去 別去 Spence 求你了
I need someone I know is real right now, all right?
我需要待在熟人身邊 好嗎?
You ok?
你還好吧?
Help me, please. Help me.
救我 求你了 救我
Help me.
救我
Scratch is down. Repeat... Scratch is down.
抓撓先生已死 重復 抓撓先生已死
He fell trying to escape.
他逃跑時摔死
We never get to say good-bye the way we want,
我們永遠無法以想要的方式告別
and when we deal with a loss so sudden and cruel,
當我們遭受殘忍突然的分離時
our emotions can overwhelm us.
悲痛鋪天蓋地覆蓋我們的心
Stephen Walker was a good agent,
Stephen Walker是個好探員
but he was a better man.
他更是一個好人
He made the world a better place,
他讓世界變得更加美好
and we can honor him by doing the work he never got to do.
我們會完成他未竟的事業來懷緬他
- There are no words. - No.
- 沒有遺囑 - 沒有
There are not.
一句也沒有
Monica, I asked Stephen to join the BAU.
Monica 我請Stephen加入BAU
I asked him to hunt Scratch.
是想讓他幫忙逮捕抓撓先生
I got him killed, and...
我害死了他
Peter Lewis killed my husband...
Peter Lewis殺了我丈夫
And I choose to believe Stephen can rest
我寧願相信 Stephen知道自己
knowing he helped this team catch him.
幫助你們抓到了他 會安息的
Thank you.
謝謝你
If there's anything the Bureau can do
如果有什麼事是局裡能夠
for you or your family, please...
幫上你或者家人的 請盡管
I will.
我會的
Right now, my kids need me...
現在 我的孩子需要我
And your team needs you.
你的團隊需要你
Ohh... Ok.
噢 沒事的
We're ok.
我們會好的
I wanted to thank you for all of your help.
我想要感謝你的大力協助
Well, it was good to be of help.
很高興能幫上忙
Ever since the IRT went down, I've been
IRT解散之後
sitting on my hands waiting for a new assignment.
我一直幹坐著等新任務呢
We should sit down tomorrow. We can talk about that.
明天我們該見個面 好好談談這件事
I'd like that.
求之不得
So we all need to discuss
我們需要討論一下
what Peter Lewis' death means for this team.
Peter Lewis的死 對團隊意味著什麼
It means that Hotch can come back.
這意味著Hotch能回來
Yeah. We spoke to him.
是的 我們跟他談過了
He was relieved that he and Jack were out of danger.
他很高興自己和Jack脫離了危險
They're out of Witness Protection,
他們不用繼續參加證人保護計劃
but, um...
但 呃
He's not coming back, is he?
他不打算回來了 是吧?
He loves being a full-time dad.
他很喜歡做全職父親
He never got to do that before,
他之前從未有機會
and... let's face it... in this job...
而且 老實說 這份工作
There's always gonna be another Scratch,
遲早要面對下一個抓撓先生
and he's lost enough.
他已經失去得夠多
We all have.
我們都一樣
Yes. We have, which is why the director has ordered us
是的 所以局長命令我們
to take some time off from handling cases,
在辦案之前先休假一段時間
but before we all leave, there's one last thing
但在放假之前 還有件事
I need to say.
我想說一下
Scratch got deeper into my head than I care to admit,
雖然不想承認 但抓撓先生弄亂了我的頭腦
and the only way I was able to stay sane
我能保持清醒的唯一方法
was by repeating a mantra, two words.
就是不停地重復兩個字
You know what those two words were?
你們知道是哪兩個字嗎?
"Wheels up."
"出發"
it saved my life when I wasn't sure I was gonna make it
在我不確定自己能否堅持時 它救了我
because it reminded me that you were out there fighting,
因為這讓我知道 你們還在努力
so take your rest... You've earned it...
所以好好休息 這是你們應得的
But when we get back,
但回來之後
wheels up, Matt.
出發 Matt
Wheels up, Emily.
出發 Emily
Wheels up, Tara.
出發 Tara
Wheels up.
出發
Damn right, wheels up.
說得好 出發
-=http://bbs. sfile2012=- Proudly Presents
<font color=#238E68-=伊甸園美劇=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流, 嚴禁用於商業途徑
Sync: YTET- °îµÂÖí
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯&校對: 米米粒愛小乖 時間軸: YTET-邦德豬